Yeah, man. We've been going. We've been
going. It's been fun. You know, it's
been fun. Brad and I have been uh you
know, we we've been back in the bunker
just uh going going at it. So, it's been
it's been fun. It really has. You know,
it's kind of a little bit of a rebirth,
actually.
>> Yep.
>> Yeah, for sure.
you know, when when uh you you feel like
not feel like when you fall short, you
know, and you feel like you've got these
pieces in certain areas, um then you
identify, okay, why why were we not able
to get over the hump in some of these
games? What was it about this or this?
What what what is going to help us get
over and and you got to look at it in
totality. I look at myself. I look at
the staff and then certainly the
players, you know, where can we get
better? Um do we need to get younger in
some areas? Felt like we needed to get
younger in some areas. That's that's
just the nature of this league, you
know. We uh we had some really good
production. Um and a lot of things from
these players that we really counted on
and and uh those guys, man, helped us a
lot. It's hard. It look hard to lose
guys like Alex and Deck and Leaf and uh
you know, Muhamad and I mean those guys
have been really good for Reer, you
know, now Reer's still out there. We'll
see. Lopez. Um but but that's the nature
of the beast, too. You're that's kind of
where we're at and uh we're in the next
kind of phase of this, you know. Um and
and then it's about what we've done.
Finding the next wave of guys that fit
those that fit St. Brown and fit SU and
golf and Branch and Jack and um Hutch.
So, you know, that complement those
guys. And so that in that sense, it's
exciting. But but we we've looked at
everything. They've been through all the
cutups, you know, from everything from
us to the the personnel.
>> Analone
just those guys that have been staples
and leaders just as a coach, how do you
kind of I mean,
>> nobody's going to doubt your culture
that you built here. How do you replace
those guys?
>> Well, it's never easy, but what what
we're saying is is that I I'm I'm
putting my eggs in the basket of Pane
Sul in that old line room. Like, he's
the leader. Um, I'm putting my eggs in
the basket of of Jack Campbell in the
linebacker room. Like, it's time. These
guys weren't just good football players
coming out of college that fit us. These
guys had leadership qualities. Now,
don't be something you're not, but we
feel like these are the guys, whether
it's vocal or it's or it's just I lead
by example. These are guys that people
will follow and they're about what we're
about. So, to me, we may be taking the
handcuffs off of some of these guys if
you ask me a little bit. It's time for
these guys to grow and take ownership of
this. Uh, and I think it actually is
going to help us in the long run. No,
that that's nothing against those guys
that were here, man. We had some really
good years and they're the ones who
helped get us where we are and where
we've been. So, and we'll be forever
grateful for that.
>> Yeah.
>> Well,
yeah, it's been great. Uh the first
thing that drew me to him was the his
tape. I I just anytime we had crossover
tape, I love what they did offensively
just and it wasn't so well, you know,
he's just he's playing in heavy. He's
playing in three. Well, that's all he
had really, you know, and a receiver, a
couple of receiver, you know, that was
kind of the world they were in. But I
love the fact that when you really watch
his tape, he's about the matchups, man.
And he's finding them wherever he can
find them. And, you know, they they um
they had some injuries, they had some,
you know, they're limited in some areas.
And I thought he maximized what they had
and what they did. And I just, you know,
when you listen to him and you sit down
with him and you listen to him talk, he
he understands quarterback play. He
understands tight end. He understands
old line. He understands receivers. He's
coached all of those. Uh so he can coach
it from the ground up, all of it. And so
that gives you good direction. That
gives the staff good direction. Here's
what I want to do, how I want to do it,
and what I want it to look like that. So
he's that point person, man. Um, and and
what I would tell you is the guy, he's
the same guy every day. He's
unbelievable. I mean, this guy is, you
know, I said, "Hey, listen. Tell me if
there's something that I I need to
know." I'm like, "Don't got something on
your mind or something you want to do? I
need to know it from you." He's like,
"All right." And he tells me, I said, "I
don't like that." And he says, "Okay, no
problem. We'll do this." I said, "I"
And it's nothing like we've been, but my
point is this guy is I mean, he he
adjusts. He's in the flow. Nothing
throws him off. He he will he's ready to
adapt, adjust, whatever you want,
whatever you need. We're gonna make it
work. We're going to maximize this. So,
he's been great, man. It's been good.
How confident are you?
>> Yeah, we we very confident. That's easy.
I mean, we I've talked to him uh that
was we are we're ready to do that if
need be. I don't want to say that. And
right now, I'm going to commit to that,
but that's I mean, we're ready to do
that. Um, you know, and all he wants is
a couple of days to work his left-handed
stance a little bit. You know, it's a
little bit like riding a bike for him.
Um, he he I he'll be fine. He'll be
fine. you know, he'll bank some reps and
be able to do it, but he he gives us
that flexibility. If you're asking me,
I'd like to move him. I would I'd like
to move him to left.
>> How nice is it having a player that
gives you that kind of flexibility? No
matter what you bring in,
he can do that.
>> It's big. You don't you don't get that
everywhere with every player. But it
also shows how special he is, you know,
and he's done it because he's he's he's
done that before. He's played left
before, you know. Hell, his first year
here with us when Decker went down, he
played left. I mean, he as a rookie, he
banked real reps against real guys at
left tackle and adapted us and he goes
to right and I know it's been years, but
yeah, there'll be a little rush maybe at
first. He He's going to be fine. The
guy's um phenomenal and he's going to
work on it until he gets it the way he
wants it to where it feels like the
right side. Why would you like him to
left
these days?
Why why is that position?
>> Yeah, I I just I think sometimes um I I
would say it's not the most important
thing like oh well, you know, the the
backside of your quarterback, you play
so much right and left-handed. You don't
you know, not everything is
right-handed. But I do think um
I do think just knowing that that Soul's
back there, you know what Decker's been
able to do for all those years, you see
some of those where he's able to anchor
in golf is kind of they're back to back
and he makes those throws, he steps up,
there's a security blanket there
subconsciously. And I just think that's
to know who's back there and to feel
like, okay, even if I feel that back or
I'm good, you know, I I just think it
brings a little extra security. Um, and
most of the time if it doesn't go that
way, at least you know where it's coming
from or you can feel it. You know, if
I'm the quarterback, it's all in front
of me.
What did that allow you guys to do?
>> It was big. Like he he was, you know, he
and Linderbomb we thought were the two.
Um so we were fired up, you know, to be
able to get him. Uh that that was big
for us, man. Being able to get that
center piece. We we feel like Maize can
anchor, you know, he can keep the pocket
clean for golf up the middle and we
don't feel restricted, you know, in the
run game. We we do feel like we can do
the pin and pulls, the wide zones, the
gaps with him. We think he's got enough
versatility and all that. And he's an
ascending center. Like he he really
hasn't played it that long. He's getting
better. Like we we felt a lot of growth
last year in that tape, you know, and
they played really good opponents, a lot
a lot of them that we played, you know,
they get in the playoffs and we just
thought he had a really steady solid
season that's ascending and we're like,
man, this guy upgrades us.
>> So we're we're fired up to get him. That
helps significantly. Coach Isaac Tesla,
he had six touchdowns and 16 receptions
last season. What do you expect from him
moving forward and what makes him
successful?
>> So, you're gonna say, "Why do you need
to throw to him more?"
>> Yeah. Why didn't you throw to
>> Yeah. I mean, the odds when you put that
in the um Yeah, we we really like Tesla.
We feel like he's he's taken off. We
feel like he was one of those guys that
really I it would you'd be hardressed to
say that he didn't make the most growth
of a rookie. Now, Tyreek did a great
job. We thought Rattlage got better, but
man, I really thought Tesla, it's not
easy for a receiver. It's not easy for
any of them, but all that we asked to
him, you know, there's some games we
lost Saint, he had to go in and play
that position right before the game, you
know, second play of the game. He's got
to go do all of it. Um, so we like him.
He's got a bright future for us.
>> Uh, what what do you think's his best
attribute? Is it route running? Is it
his hands?
>> His hair.
>> He can do it all. Uh, he's tough. He's
tough. He's big. I I would say catch
radius, you know, that's one of the best
things that just his abil body control
and catch radius, you know, um is I
think kind of his trick, man. That's his
So, we we like him a lot.
>> Hey, Dan, I want to ask you about AG and
then obviously
>> Hold on one second. Hold on one second.
>> Yeah, I'll come right back to you.
curious. I guess kind of classifying
this as third line
Alex.
>> Y
the shifting defensive packages you guys
were really
y
>> Yeah. So here here's what we you know we
I told you guys the combine I I was back
there with the defense. We were going
through all those cutups from last year
you know with Shep and and the staff. I
love that staff. All right.
There's so many things that you take in,
you're like, "All right, you know, what
did we do well? What did we not? Where
do we go from here? You know, this this
is who we lost. Uh here's some pieces
that we added. What do we need?" And so
really the way chef's done it, which I
love, is we've kind of we've kind of
given ourselves we got kind of these
three options a little bit as to where
we can go with this. It's still us, but
it gives us dependent on who the other
end is, you know, okay, we got won them.
Do we draft somebody? All right, what
does it look like? Are we more of this
four down? Do we become more five down?
Do we become more nickel depending on
So, we've got some flexibility here.
Ready? Like it it's already built into
the install for Shep. Like, all right, I
can go three ways here by personnel.
It's still the same install, but we just
now we got the pieces to put where we
want, whether that's a nickel, it's an
end, it's a big end. Um, it's a
linebacker.
So, we we we're kind of flexible here,
you know. We we got some flexibility.
So, yes, we love base because it
dictates, but not if we don't have the
personnel to play bass, you know. Now,
that being said, it was it was big
getting Rodrigo back, you know, that
helps. That gives us some flexibility
there. um you know with Jack and Barnes
you know but we we look we still got
work to do too there there's no secret
there
>> I forgot about you
>> what has he said about
>> yeah I mean we we've probably everything
you guys know I mean it was we've we got
all the information um that that says he
wasn't involved that's what we know
that's all we know um
And I mean, that's really all I can say.
I mean, we're monitoring what what's out
there. I mean, as of a month ago, I the
uh this was this was an this was
nothing, you know. He he So, I I I have
no idea what this is. Uh as far as I
know, it's still not a big deal. It
seems like, you know, he wasn't involved
with this. Um
>> so,
>> steps, if any, you have to take to just
make sure you have some insurance in
case you know, things change.
Well, I yeah, getting Rock was big, you
know. Um, getting Rock back was big for
us, you know. Now, that's not why Well,
what happens if that wasn't the thought?
Um, but, you know, it if if it happens
that way, um, or you talk about
insurance, I mean, certainly we'll need
we'll need to be able to fill in
somewhere with depth, but look, we still
got Reed. Um, we like Rake. Rake's
coming back. I know it's unproven right
now, but uh he's had a good off
seasonason to this point, you know, and
uh and we got Rock, man, and McCra. And
so we we've got some things there. Um
and we'll just take it as it comes. I
mean, I until something happens, I I
feel like we're going to be good here. I
you know, I'm going to trust what the
kids said and think we're all right.
trying to play outside inside.
>> Yeah, I you know, right now I see Rake
more outside than anything, you know,
and let him compete. And I know it's
look, it's early, but that's why we
draft him to see if he can uh he can
fill one of these roles or or compete
for us.
>> T your perspective on
>> Hold on one second.
>> All right. AG uh obviously had a tough
first year with the Jets, too. You had a
similar type of experience your first
year in Detroit. What did you learn from
that experience going in your first and
second year? What do you think AG will
learn?
>> Well, that AG and I were talking again
yesterday and uh it was funny because we
were kind of talking about the season a
little bit and and now here you are
going into year two. Man, they got a lot
of capital, a lot of value, ready to go,
you know, made some moves in free agency
that fit what AG's about. And I'm like,
well, this is nothing new for you, AG.
He lived it with us. I mean, we we it's
damn near the same thing. I mean, we
went through this a little bit. So, uh,
and what you learn is, man, stay true to
what you believe in. Don't don't start
going the other way or doing something
you don't believe in. That's where you
get in trouble. You believed in it when
you took that job. When you told the
owner what you want to do, you told the
fans, you told these players, "Keep
going." Like, push right through it,
man. You'll push through that wall. It
took us, you know, whatever that was,
seven games um before we got through it
in year two, but we got through it. And,
um, the most important thing is to do
what you believe in with the guys you
believe in.
those lines. Pen had a pretty immediate
Oh, I'm sorry. Go ahead.
>> Dan, your perspective on the David
McGomery trade and what kind of impact
you think you can make. The Texans
wanted to be that RB1 Below kind of guy.
>> Yeah, I love David McGomery. He's a
stud. He's unbelievable. Um, and you
know, this is something we had a
conversation after and, you know, felt
like he this was something that was
going to be good for both sides. You
know, this gave David an opportunity to
be the bail cow and uh we got some value
back. Uh, I love Dave. He's a freaking
pro, man. He is unbelievable. So, we He
will be missed, but I think the Houston
Texans are gonna be very happy with the
back they just got. I think he makes
them better.
It it's hard, you know, it's hard
because you you understand what they,
you know, what they do, uh, and all that
they give um, you know, to to do it the
right way to make it work to, you know,
to try to they buy into the vision.
They, you know, and so when you lose
those guys, it's hard because the other
thing it's just, it's abrupt, right? It
just, it's like David. He asked about
David. You know, we talked right when
everything happened and I love him to
death and but that's it. You know, now
we'll talk again at some point, but it's
just these guys you're around all the
time. It's like coaches, man. They're
just it's just gone. And it's crazy,
man. It's crazy. But but that's the
nature of the business. And that's the
way it was when I was a player. You
know, some of these coaches, it's like
had a coach that it was like we talked
every day, man. He he would send me
messages. He would talk. he would all
and then the minute I go to another team
I never heard from him again you know
and it wasn't being vindictive but it's
also a little bit like well you're not
part of the team anymore and I my all my
focus is on this and that's kind of the
world we live in unfortunately it it's
hard you know but it is the that's
that's the way it goes
>> yeah there there was a there was a path
um you know it it was you know it was on
reduced reduced price, but um yeah, we
we were willing to but we knew we needed
help, too, you know, and that was kind
of a little bit of uh with with Decker
and Dave, we get some capital to where
now we can use on free agents. I mean,
you know, Decker's alone with the way it
all went down, we got three players that
we feel like are going to help us, you
know, that we wouldn't have gotten, you
know, um once he
um but listen, Deck Deck's a stud, man.
He he gave a lot for a long time through
three regimes and uh be forever grateful
man and uh he'll always be a line and
it'll always be his home at some point
you know so um he'll be missed like all
those guys will be missing
how big
you get
ready
Yeah, I think that's always the case.
You know, you you want to make sure you
get guys that fit what you're about and
man, they got something to prove. You
know, I I think that because that really
fits what we talked about that fits the
rest of those guys in that locker room
that we know are going to be here long
term. Um that's kind of what we're we're
about, you know, and and getting back to
a little bit of that. Um you know, look,
everybody wants talent. Oh, all I want
talent, but it's always nice to have a
little bit of saltiness to you. Um,
over the talent that lacks saltiness
because that's kind of what we were in
22, you know, that's a little bit of in
part of 23. We had talent, but we were
all we had some salty guys, man. And we
were highly competitive and we were
willing to make it work, figure it out.
And so just a little bit of that edge
back, you know, and some of that comes
with youth, you know, now with youth,
you're going to have some of the stuff
that gets frustrating, right? The the
mentals, the but but we we believe we
can get them there as a staff and with
the rest of the players we have around
them.
>> Oh, we I cover Ben with the Bears.
>> Oh, okay.
>> How is the challenge different when
you've had that first taste of success?
You talk about, you know, kind of took
you a while to get over the hump, but
once you get there, then what's the
challenge? can
>> a head coach.
>> Yeah. Winning a Super Bowl. I mean
that's the next winning the next one.
You know that that's always it. So I
mean that that's that's what we're in.
Um
>> and so it's what you realize is last
year was not good enough. Like what we
did in 22 was not good enough, right?
And so 23 you improve. Well, what you
did in 23 is not good enough for 24.
Well, 24 you improve to a sense yet you
don't. And then you take a step. You're
constantly trying to look. We're all
trying to You want to win Super Bowl and
you want to win multiple Super Bowls. If
you want to do what Bellich did, Andy
Reid, yeah, all these guys, if you can,
I mean, that's what we're in it for. Um
cuz ultimately, there's nothing sicker
than, man, you're you're finding wins,
you're winning, deep down, you're like,
we don't match up with anybody in the
playoffs,
>> right?
>> Like that's a sickening feeling, you
know, and uh you you don't want to be
there, you know? You don't you don't So,
you're always trying to improve and and
get over the hump. Knowing Ben the way
you do, you think he's wired the right
way to be able to tackle those
challenges?
>> Oh, for sure. Ben Ben will be fine. Um,
Ben's highly driven. He's very smart,
highly competitive. Um, you know, he's
going to be a force to be dealt with in
this division and NFC for for a long
time to come.
>> Yep. Yep.
>> Say it again.
>> Yeah. Uh, he he's big in for us. So we
play base, he can play the five or the
four eye five tech over the tackle and
then he can kick down into the three
technique. You know that those are kind
of where he goes. You know, every once
in a while we playing a four down like
nickel defense. He can play opposite of
Hutch like on first down. You know, they
like to run to the tight end. We'll put
Levi over there, you know, if it So
that's kind of his role. And he can also
go and swing at the nose if we need it.
Like he can play the nose. You know,
he's a big strong athletic man as we all
know. It'll be about, you know, him. How
does uh, you know, how is all this is he
able to stay healthy? You know, can we
get through this? But if he can, we we
think Levi can, you know, be a good
player.
>> He he's really like a rush in. He's a
DN. So, he's he's the guy you put
opposite of Huts in a true four down.
You know, if he's playing in base
defense, it may be to spell Hutch for a
play or two. You know, he takes that
role on. So, he's more of that. He's not
like the big end in base that gets over
a tackle with Barnes outside of him.
That's not fair to ask him to do all
that. Now, he'll battle.
>> He He'll battle. Well, we we believe he
can get an edge, but he Here's what I
would say with Wanom. And, you know, we
played against him at Minnesota. I mean,
he caught our eye two years, three years
ago, whatever that was. The guy is I
mean, he plays the run. He's tough. He's
physical. He's smart. He's versatile.
And he can get an edge every once in a
while. And he can play special teams if
you need him.
>> Okay. And what did you think about the
flag football uh experience last weekend
when the amateurs and the
>> I I didn't see it. I I did not see it.
Now Shawn Peyton filled me in on
everything yesterday. So I I've kind of
got an idea.
>> Any surprise on on the level of
competition being so lopsided?
>> Well, I think it's like any other sport.
You know, you ask uh you ask a player to
go to a kind of another sport and you
know, things get a little bit different.
You ask an NFL player to go play hockey.
All right. You ask a hockey player to go
play basketball in the NBA, you you
know, and I think flag football's a
little bit of that, too. I think it's a
unique athlete. I think they're
jitterbugs are the ones that they're low
center of gravity, they got speed, they
got agility. Um, so it's interesting.
>> Luke Keequley should not have been a
high draft pick uh in that Wednesday
thing. What what are your thoughts on
NFL guys doing this and maybe the risk
of injury or anything like that if they
wanted to continue to
>> Yeah, I I mean I I think there is going
to be that that's a little scary. I
think you know you got to you as a club
you got to think through it. We got to
think through it. Um but but ultimately
I I
>> I'll be honest with you. I don't lose
any sleep thinking about it. All right.
I
>> So
yeah, you bet. You bet.
>> Ask about David.
>> Hold on. Hold on.
>> There's been a lot of talk about
positional value in the draft. You guys
took Gibbs as early as you did. What was
the thought process for you guys? What
is the impact?
>> Yeah. Well, Gibbs, we didn't view Gibbs
as a runner. We He was a weapon, you
know. He He was a weapon, man. He was u
It's a little bit like J Mo, like we we
didn't necessarily view JMO as a true
receiver. We we saw more weaponry. So, a
lot of versatility, things you can do.
And so, that's why it was we felt like
Gibbs, man, this guy is going to
explode. Like, yes, he's a runner. He
can run all schemes. He can run inside,
outside, pin and pull the perimeters,
but he's also he can be lethal out of
the back field. And we're not even there
yet. We feel like this guy can play some
receiver. You know, we tried to tinker
with some stuff last year. He really
grew, but I think we're just scratching
the surface of some of that. He he's
he's a you know he he's a mismatch piece
man and he is uh he's dynamic
and he's a differencemaker.
>> They don't come around often.
>> No no we would have taken him earlier.
We would have taken him earlier. So
yeah,
>> what does that look like?
>> Well, I I think it it just
I think it's a little bit like, you
know, there
let's focus on winning games. Let's not
beat ourselves. This is how we're going
to do it. It may not be easy all the
time, guys. And we may do some things
that are a little bit more um
Look, I don't want to get too far into
this because you got to see what kind of
team you have, where you go, but but I
guess what I'm saying, man, I want I
want to go back to what we did a little
bit and let's get our confidence back
up. Let's not beat ourselves. Uh let's
make sure that our calling card is what
we said. It's about grit and everything
starts with grit. And then we'll work
from there. you know, now once we're
able to uh to get a little lethal and be
more potent in some areas and be more
aggressive, we're going to do that, you
know, but um
I just want to make sure that we're
we're saying what we are, you know, that
we believe in what we really are and
it's not lip service, that's all. when
you guys
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. I mean, you don't want you never
want a player to feel like uh
something's happened to them that they
don't feel good about. I mean, you don't
want that, you know. Um, but I'll go
back to what I said, man. I look, I I'm
going to give nothing but flowers to
Deck, but for everything he did for us
and what he's done for this
organization. Um, and look, I
I'm I'm sure as hell not going to call
him right now, not after all this
article came out, but I'll call him, you
know, I'm going to call him in time. Uh,
but I want him to know it's real and
it's a real phone call. Um, but man, we
appreciate everything he did.
Tan, uh, when you had David Blau, do you
see a future coach? And now, third
quarter, what do you recall about your
own transition to that first time play
call?
>> Yeah. Well, Blau was always kind of a
coach for us as a third quarterback. I
mean, he did a lot of things to help us.
He did a lot of things to help out um
golf, you know, we give him projects. I
mean, so his mind's always been wired
that way. He was always ready to play
and his mind has always thought that
way, you know. Um, so what was the
second part of that question? Do you
recall your transition to becoming a
first- time play caller or things that
you know?
>> Yeah, I mean it it it's unique. You
know, it takes you a minute to get in
the rhythm and kind of find your way and
where you want to go with it. Um but but
you pick up on it fast and Blau's going
to he'll take off, man. You know, you
got to have the pre you got training
camp, you got offseason, you got
training camp, you got preseason games.
Like he'll be cooking, you know. And
look, inevitably, I don't care how good
you are, you're going to make a call
that is not the right call and the
players got to adjust and they got to
bail you out. I don't care who it is or
where it is. And so Bl's going to do a
great job. I I think he's I think he's
going to be a superstar, man. I really
do.
>> D, I just wanted to ask you real quick
about um Ben Johnson and uh your
relationship with him now and how he's
matured as a coach.
>> Yeah, it it's a good relationship. Um
you know, we talked yesterday. Um, you
know, it's look, man, we we still our
families were around each other, you
know, his kids, his wife, u him, I mean,
when you're with somebody, as long as I
was with Ben, you're going to have a
relationship. Now, when you know, when
we play each other, we won't we want to
beat the crap out of each other. That's
the nature of the business. But, but
that doesn't mean he's not a friend,
man. And I don't care for him and and
want to help him as long as it doesn't
hurt us. And I'm sure he'd tell you the
same thing. So, got a lot of respect for
Ben, man.
We always ask
>> Yeah, we're not doing it. Not going to
do it, man. Yep. Yep. Not going to do
it.
>> Yep. Uh I just felt like, man, as this
has gone on, you know, I felt like we
got two really good years of it, man.
Like, wow, man, we're really getting
some out out of this. I really uh were
and then as it, you know, as it kind of
went on, we got into that third year,
you know, whatever that was, or 24, I
don't know, it it just felt
counterproductive, man. It didn't feel
like we were getting what I thought we
would get out of it. Uh and and part of
me was like, you know, I think we would
have gotten more we'd have gotten extra
practice and we'd have gotten more done
had we just gone against ourselves. And
so I I want to kind of keep this let's
just keep it about us. Let's go to work,
you know, set the schedule up and we can
hit everything. We don't have to get
ready for the next opponent in a joint
practice. We go right through, man. We
got first down, we got third down, we
got red zone, we got backed up, we got
four-minute, we got two minute, we got
situational work, got special teams
involved, uh, mock games, and let's
let's just go and then maybe we play
some of these guys in the preseason more
than we have. You know, that's where
they get some of it. Um,
>> Germany, I don't know if you've been
overseas,
>> been to London three times.
>> Yeah, I I'm still wrestling with that,
Dave. Honestly, I go back and forth,
man. Um I've been trying to pitch the
idea to get a um you know, let's just
buy a cruise ship right after that last
game. Jump on the cruise ship and we'll
just adapt as we go over, man. We go up,
we walk through on the deck, man. We got
the hot tubs, the pools, recovery rooms.
We can game plan on the way. Uh I I
don't feel like anybody's taking it,
though. And uh and I had uh I had a
coach inform me. He's like, you know,
it's so many nautical miles, it's going
to take 8 days to get there. I'm like,
just keep your mouth shut.
So, I don't think that's going to
happen, but we'll see. So, I I'm
bouncing that around. I've done both.
Um, you know, played well with both,
lost with both, you know, basically.
It's like, man, went out there a week,
we we won one time, went out there a
week, we got throttled, then we went out
on a Thursday, played well, you know.
So, um, I know this, it's you're going
to do whatever you think you can do and
whatever you're not willing to give it
into. So the team that's got the most
energy, the most use, doesn't use
excuses, is probably going to have a
good chance to win that game.
>> Thank you guys. We got to run. Thank
you.
>> Yeah, I'm sure AI is already on it.